PATRICK WINSTON: Welcome to 6034.
PATRICK WINSTON：欢迎来到 6034。
I don't know if I can deal with this microphone.
我不知道我是否可以处理这个麦克风。
We'll see what happens.
我们会看看会发生什么。
It's going to be a good year.
这将是一个好年头。
We've got [INAUDIBLE] a bunch of interesting people.
我们有 [听不清]一群有趣的人。
It's always interesting to see what people named their
看看二十年前人们给他们的孩子取什么名字总是很有趣的
children two decades ago.
。
And I find they were overwhelmed with Emilys.
我发现他们对 Emilys 不知所措。
And there are not too many Peters, Pauls, and Marys, but
彼得斯、保罗斯和玛丽斯并不多，但
enough to call forth a suitable song at some point.
足以在某个时候召唤出一首合适的歌曲。
We have lots of Jesses of both genders.
我们有很多男女皆宜的杰西。
We have a [INAUDIBLE]
我们有两个性别的[听不清
of both genders.
]。
And we have a Duncan, where's Duncan?
我们有一个邓肯，邓肯呢？
There you are, Duncan.
你来了，邓肯。
You've changed your hairstyle.
你换了发型。
I want to assure use that the Thane of Cawdor is not taking
我想向大家保证，考多的领主本学期没有
the course this semester.
上这门课。
What I'm going to do is tell you about artificial
我今天要做的是告诉你关于人工智能的
intelligence today, and what this subject is about.
事情，以及这个主题是关于什么的。
There's been about a 10% percent turnover in the roster
在过去的 24 小时内，球员名单的更替率约为 10%
in the last 24 hours.
。
I expect another 10% turnover in the next 24 hours, too.
我预计在接下来的 24 小时内还会有 10% 的营业额。
So I know many of you are sightseers, wanting to know if
所以我知道你们中的许多人都是观光客，想知道
this is something you want to do.
这是否是你想做的事情。
So I'm going to tell you about what we're going to do this
所以我要告诉你这个学期我们要做
semester, and what you'll know when you get out of here.
什么，以及当你离开这里时你会知道什么。
I'm going to walk you through this outline.
我将引导你完成这个大纲。
I'm going to start by talking about what artificial
我将首先讨论什么是
intelligence is, and why we do it.
人工智能，以及我们为什么要这样做。
And then I'll give you a little bit of the history of
然后我会给你一点人工智能的历史
artificial intelligence, and conclude with some of the
，并
covenants by which we run the course.
以我们运行课程的一些约定作为结束。
One of which is no laptops, please.
其中之一是没有笔记本电脑，拜托。
I'll explain why we have these covenants at the end.
最后我会解释为什么我们有这些契约。
So what is it?
那是什么？
Well, it must have something to do with thinking.
嗯，它一定与思考有关。
So let's start up here, a definition of artificial
所以让我们从这里开始，人工智能的定义
intelligence, by saying that it's about thinking,
，说它是关于思考的，
whatever that is.
不管那是什么。
My definition of artificial intelligence has
我对人工智能的定义
to be rather broad.
必须相当广泛。
So we're going to say it's not only about thinking.
所以我们要说这不仅仅是关于思考。
It's also about perception, and it's about action.
这也关乎感知，关乎行动。
And if this were a philosophy class, then I'd stop right
如果这是一堂哲学课，那么我会停
there and just say, in this subject we're going to talk
在那里，只是说，在这个主题中，我们将讨论
about problems involving thinking,
涉及思考、
perception, and action.
感知和行动的问题。
But this is not a philosophy class.
但这不是哲学课。
This a Course six class.
这是六门课。
It's an engineering school class.
这是工程学校的课。
It's an MIT class.
这是麻省理工学院的课程。
So we need more than that.
所以我们需要的不止这些。
And therefore we're going to talk about models that are
因此，我们将讨论
targeted at thinking, perception, and action.
针对思考、感知和行动的模型。
And this should not be strange to you, because model making
这对你来说应该不奇怪，因为模型制作
is what MIT is about.
是麻省理工学院的主题。
You run into someone at a bar, or relative asks you what you
你在酒吧遇到某人，或者亲戚问
do at MIT, the right knee jerk reaction is to say, we learned
你在麻省理工学院做什么，右膝跳动的反应是说，我们学会了
how to build models.
如何建立模型。
That's what we do at MIT.
这就是我们在麻省理工学院所做的。
We build the models using differential equations.
我们使用微分方程建立模型。
We build models using probabilities.
我们使用概率构建模型。
We build models using physical and computational simulations.
我们使用物理和计算模拟来构建模型。
Whatever we do, we build models.
无论我们做什么，我们都会建立模型。
Even in humanities class, MIT approach is to make models
即使在人文课上，麻省理工学院的方法是制作
that we can use to explain the past, predict the future,
我们可以用来解释过去、预测未来、
understand the subject, and control the world.
理解主题和控制世界的模型。
That's what MIT is about.
这就是麻省理工学院的意义所在。
And that's what this subject is about, too.
这也是这个主题的主题。
And now, our models are models of thinking.
现在，我们的模型是思维模型。
So you might say, if I take this
所以你可能会说，如果我拿这个
classic will I get smarter?
经典，我会变得更聪明吗？
And the answer is yes.
答案是肯定的。
You will get smarter.
你会变得更聪明。
Because you'll have better models of your own thinking,
因为你会有更好的自己思维模型，
not just the subject matter of the subject, but better models
不仅仅是主题的主题，还有
of your own thinking.
你自己思维的更好模型。
So models targeted at thinking,
因此，模型以思考、
perception, and action.
感知和行动为目标。
We know that's not quite enough, because in order to
我们知道这还不够，因为为了
have a model, you have to have representation.
有一个模型，你必须有代表性。
So let's say that artificial intelligence is about
因此，假设人工智能是关于
representations that support the making of models to
支持模型制作的表示，以
facilitate an understanding of thinking,
促进对思维、
perception, and action.
感知和行动的理解。
Now you might say to me, well what's a representation?
现在你可能会对我说，那么什么是表示？
And what good can it do?
它有什么好处？
So I'd like to take a brief moment to tell you about
所以我想花一点时间来告诉你关于
gyroscopes.
陀螺仪的事情。
Many of you have friends in mechanical engineering.
你们中的许多人都有机械工程方面的朋友。
One of the best ways embarrass them is to say here's a
让他们难堪的最好方法之一就是说这是一个
bicycle wheel.
自行车轮子。
And if I spin it, and blow hard on it right here, on the
如果我旋转它，并在这里，在轮子的边缘用力吹它，会朝
edge of the wheel, is going to turn over
this way or this way?
这个方向还是朝这个方向翻？
I guarantee that what they will do is they'll put their
我保证他们会做的是他们将
hand in an arthritic posture called the right hand screw
手放在一个称为右手螺旋
rule, aptly named because people who use it tend to get
规则的关节炎姿势，恰当地命名是因为使用它的人倾向于在
the right answer about 50% of the time.
大约50% 的时间里得到正确的答案。
But we're never going to make that mistake again.
但我们永远不会再犯这个错误了。
Because we're electrical engineers,
因为我们是电气工程师，
not mechanical engineers.
而不是机械工程师。
And we know about representation.
我们知道代表。
What we're going to do is we're going to think about it
我们要做的
a little bit.
是稍微考虑一下。
And we're going to use some duct tape to help us think
我们将使用一些胶带来帮助我们
about just one piece of the wheel.
只考虑一个轮子。
So I want you to just think about that piece of the wheel
所以我想让你想想
as the wheel comes flying over the top, and I
当轮子飞过顶部时轮子的那块，我
blow on it like that.
就这样吹。
What's going to happen to that one piece?
那一件会发生什么？
It's going to go off that way, right?
它会这样下去，对吧？
And the next piece is going to go off that way too.
下一段也将以这种方式进行。
So when it comes over, it has to go that way.
所以当它过来的时候，它必须走那条路。
Let me do some ground f here just to be sure.
为了确定，让我在这里做一些基础。
It's very powerful feeling.
这是一种非常强大的感觉。
Try it.
试试看。
We need a demonstration.
我们需要一个示范。
I don't anybody think that I'm cheating, here.
我没有人认为我在作弊，在这里。
So let's just twist it one way or the other.
因此，让我们以一种或另一种方式扭转它。
So that's powerful pull, isn't it.
所以这是强大的拉力，不是吗。
Alex is now never going to get the gyroscope wrong, because
亚历克斯现在永远不会弄错陀螺仪，因为
he's got the right representation.
他得到了正确的表示。
So much of what you're going to accumulate in this subject
您将在本主题中积累的大部分内容
is a suite of representations that will help you to build
是一组表示，它们将帮助您构建
programs that are intelligent.
智能程序。
But I want to give you a second example, one a little
但我想给你第二个例子，一个
bit more computational.
计算量更大的例子。
But one of which was very familiar to you by the time
但在大多数情况下，当你上一年级时，其中一个对你来说已经很熟悉了
you went to first grade, in most cases.
。
It's the problem of the farmer, the fox, the goose,
这是农民、狐狸、鹅
and the grain.
和谷物的问题。
There's a river, a leaky rowboat that can only carry
有一条河，一艘漏水的划艇，只能
the farmer, and one of his four possessions.
载着农夫，以及他的四样财产之一。
So what's the right
那么这个问题的正确
representation for this problem?
表示是什么？
It might be a picture of the farmer.
这可能是农民的照片。
It might be a poem about the situation, perhaps a haiku.
它可能是一首关于这种情况的诗，也可能是一首俳句。
We know that those are not the right representation.
我们知道那些不是正确的代表。
Somehow, we get the sense that the right representation most
不知何故，我们感觉到正确的表示最
involve something about the location of the participants
涉及在这个场景中参与者的位置
in this scenario.
。
So we might draw a picture that looks like this.
所以我们可能会画一张像这样的图片。
There's the scenario, and here in glorious green,
有这样的场景，这里是绿色的，
representing our algae infested rivers is the river.
代表我们藻类出没的河流是河流。
And here's the farmer, the fox, the goose, and the grain.
这是农夫、狐狸、鹅和谷物。
An initial situation.
初始情况。
Now there are other situations like this one, for example.
例如，现在还有其他类似的情况。
We have the river, and the farmer, and the
我们有河，有农夫，
goose is on that side.
鹅就在那边。
And the fox and the grain is on that side.
狐狸和谷物在那边。
And we know that the farmer can execute a movement from
而且我们知道农民可以执行从
one situation to another.
一种情况到另一种情况的运动。
So now we're getting somewhere where with the problem.
所以现在我们正在解决问题的地方。
This is at MIT approach to the farmer, fox,
这是麻省理工学院解决农民、狐狸、
goose, and grain problem.
鹅和谷物问题的方法。
It might have stumped you when you were a little kid.
当你还是个孩子的时候，它可能会难倒你。
How many such situations are there?
这样的情况有多少？
What do you think, Tanya?
坦尼娅，你怎么看？
It looks to me like all four of individuals can be on one
在我看来，这四个人都可以站在
side or the other.
一边或另一边。
So for every position the farmer can be, each of the
所以对于农夫的每一个位置，其他每一个
other things can be on either side of the river.
东西都可以在河的两边。
So it would be two to the fourth she says aggressively
因此，她毫不犹豫地咄咄逼人地说，应该是二到四次
and without hesitation.
。
Yes, two to the fourth, 16 possibilities.
是的，从二到四，16 种可能性。
So we could actually draw out the entire graph.
所以我们实际上可以画出整个图表。
It's small enough.
它足够小。
There's another position over here with the farmer, fox,
这里还有一个职位，农夫、狐狸、
goose, and grain.
鹅和谷物。
And in fact that's the one we want.
事实上，这正是我们想要的。
And if we draw out the entire graph, it looks like this.
如果我们画出整个图表，它看起来像这样。
This is a graph of the situations and the allowed
这是情况和
connections between them.
它们之间允许的连接的图表。
Why are there not 16?
为什么没有16个？
Because the other--
因为另一个——
how many have I got?
我有多少？
Four?
四？
10?
10？
The others are situations in which somebody gets eaten.
其他是有人被吃掉的情况。
So we don't want to go to any of those places.
所以我们不想去那些地方。
So having got the representation, something
所以得到了代表，
magical has happened.
神奇的事情发生了。
We've got our constraints exposed.
我们已经暴露了我们的约束。
And that's why we build representations.
这就是我们构建表示的原因。
That's whey you algebra in high school, because algebraic
这就是你在高中时的代数，因为代数
notation exposes the constraints that make it
符号暴露了一些限制，使你
possible to actually figure out how many customers you get
可以实际计算出你在报纸
for the number of advertisements you place in
上投放的广告数量获得了多少客户
the newspaper.
。
So artificial intelligence is about constraints exposed by
因此，人工智能是关于
representations that support models targeted to thinking--
支持以思维为目标的模型的表示所暴露的约束——
actually there's one more thing, too.
实际上还有一件事。
Not quite done.
还没有完成。
Because after all, in the end, we have to build programs.
因为归根结底，我们必须构建程序。
So it's about algorithms enabled by constraints exposed
因此，它是关于
by representations that model targeted thinking, perception,
由对目标思维、感知
and action.
和行动建模的表示所暴露的约束所启用的算法。
So these algorithms, or we might call them just as well
所以这些算法，或者我们可以将它们称为
procedures, or we might call them just as well methods,
程序，或者我们可以将它们称为方法，
whatever you like.
无论您喜欢什么。
These are the stuff of what artificial intelligence is
这些就是人工智能的内容——
about-- methods, algorithms, representations.
方法、算法、表示。
I'd like to give you one more example.
我想再给你举一个例子。
It's something we call, in artificial intelligence,
在人工智能中，我们称之为
generated test.
生成测试。
And it's such a simple idea, you'll never hear it again in
这是一个如此简单的想法，你再也不会在
this subject.
这个主题中听到它了。
But it's an idea you need to add to your repertoire of
但这是一个你需要添加到你的
problem solving methods, techniques, procedures, and
问题解决方法、技术、程序和
algorithms.
算法库中的想法。
So here's how it works.
这就是它的工作原理。
Maybe I can explain to best by starting off with an example.
也许我可以从一个例子开始最好地解释。
Here's a tree leaf I picked off a tree on
这是我在去上课的路上从一棵树上摘下来的树叶
the way over to class.
。
I hope it's not the last of the species.
我希望它不是最后一个物种。
What is it, what kind of tree?
这是什么树，什么样的树？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I never did learn my trees, or my colors, or my
我从来没有学过我的树，我的颜色，或者我的
multiplication tables.
乘法表。
So I have to go back to this book, the Audubon Society
所以我必须回到这本书，奥杜邦协会
Field Guide to North American Trees.
北美树木实地指南。
And how would I solve the problem?
我将如何解决这个问题？
It's pretty simple.
这很简单。
I just turn the pages one at a time, until I find something
我只是一次翻一页，直到找到
that looks like this leaf.
看起来像这片叶子的东西。
And then I discover it's a sycamore, or something.
然后我发现它是梧桐树之类的。
MIT's full of them.
麻省理工学院到处都是。
So when I do that, I do something very intuitive, very
所以当我这样做时，我会做一些非常直观、非常
natural, something you do all the time.
自然的事情，你一直在做的事情。
But we're going to give it a name.
但我们要给它一个名字。
We're going to call it generate and test.
我们将把它称为生成和测试。
And generate and test method consists of generating some
生成和测试方法包括生成一些
possible solutions, feeding them into a box that tests
可能的解决方案，将它们输入到一个测试它们的盒子中
them, and then out the other side comes mostly failures.
，然后从另一边出来主要是失败。
But every once in a while we get something that succeeds
但每隔一段时间，我们就会得到一些成功
and pleases us.
并让我们满意的东西。
That's what I did with the leaf.
这就是我对叶子所做的。
But now you have a name for it.
但现在你有了它的名字。
Once you have a name for something, you
一旦你为某事命名，你
get power over it.
就会获得对它的控制权。
You can start to talk about it.
你可以开始谈论它。
So I can say, if you're doing a generate and test approach
所以我可以说，如果你正在对问题进行生成和测试方法
to a problem, you better build a generator with certain
，你最好构建一个具有某些属性的生成器，这些
properties that make generators good.
属性使生成器变得更好。
For example, they should not be redundant.
例如，它们不应该是多余的。
They shouldn't give you the same solution twice.
他们不应该两次给你相同的解决方案。
They should be informable.
他们应该是知情的。
They should be able to absorb information such as, this is a
他们应该能够吸收信息，例如，这是一棵
deciduous tree.
落叶树。
Don't bother looking at the conifers.
不要费心去看针叶树。
So once you have a name for something, you can start
所以一旦你有了一个名字，你就可以开始
talking about.
谈论了。
And that vocabulary gives you power.
那个词汇给了你力量。
So we call this the Rumpelstiltskin Principle
因此，我们称其为Rumpelstiltskin 原则，
perhaps The first of our powerful ideas for the day.
也许是我们今天的第一个强有力的想法。
This subject is full of powerful ideas.
这个主题充满了强大的思想。
There will be some in every class.
每个班级都会有一些。
Rumpelstiltskin Principle says that once you can name
Rumpelstiltskin 原则说，一旦你可以命名
something, you get power over it.
某物，你就可以控制它。
You know what that little thing is on
你知道
the end of your shoelace?
鞋带末端的那个小东西是什么吗？
It's interesting.
这真有趣。
She's gesturing like mad.
她像疯了似的打手势。
That's something we'll talk about later, too--
这也是我们稍后会讨论的东西——
motor stuff, and how it helps us think.
电机的东西，以及它如何帮助我们思考。
What is it?
它是什么？
No one knows?
没人知道？
It's an ag something, right?
这是一个ag的东西，对吧？
It's an aglet, very good.
是带子的，很不错。
So once you have the name, you can start to talk about.
所以一旦你有了名字，你就可以开始谈论了。
You can say the purpose of an aglet is pretty much like the
你可以说肩带的目的很像
whipping on the end of a rope.
在绳子末端的鞭打。
It keeps the thing from unwinding.
它可以防止事情展开。
Now you have a place to hang that knowledge.
现在你有地方挂这些知识了。
So we're talking about this frequently from now into the
因此，从现在到
rest of the semester, the power of being
本学期剩下的时间，我们经常谈论这个，
able to name things.
能够命名事物的力量。
Symbolic labels give us power over concepts.
符号标签赋予我们超越概念的力量。
While we're here I should also say that this is a very simple
当我们在这里时，我还应该说这是一个非常简单的
idea, generate and test.
想法，生成和测试。
And you might be tempted to say to someone, we learned
您可能很想对某人说，我们
about generate and test today.
今天学习了生成和测试。
But it's a trivial idea.
但这是一个微不足道的想法。
The word trivial is a word I would like you to purge from
琐碎这个词是我希望你从
your vocabulary, because it's a very dangerous label.
你的词汇表中清除的一个词，因为它是一个非常危险的标签。
The reason it's dangerous is because there's a difference
它之所以危险，是因为
between trivial and simple.
琐碎和简单之间存在差异。
What is it?
它是什么？
What's the difference between labeling something as trivial
将某事标记为微不足道
and calling it simple?
和称其为简单有什么区别？
Yes?
是的？
Exactly so.
正是如此。
He says that simple can be powerful, and trivial makes it
他说简单可以很强大，而微不足道的事情
sound like it's not only simple, but of little worth.
听起来不仅简单，而且毫无价值。
So many MIT people miss opportunities, because they
很多麻省理工学院的人错过了机会，因为
have a tendency to think that ideas aren't important unless
他们倾向于认为想法不重要，除非
they're complicated.
它们很复杂。
But the most simple ideas in artificial intelligence are
但人工智能中最简单的想法
often the most powerful.
往往是最强大的。
We could teach an artificial intelligence course to you
我们可以教给你一门
that would be so full of mathematics it would make a
充满数学的人工智能课程，这会让第
Course 18 professor gag.
18 课的教授感到厌烦。
But those ideas would be merely gratuitously
但这些想法只是无缘无故地
complicated, and gratuitously mathematical, and gratuitously
复杂，无缘无故地数学化，而且无缘无故地
not simple.
不简单。
Simple ideas are often the most powerful.
简单的想法往往是最强大的。
So where are we so far?
那么到目前为止，我们在哪里？
We talked about the definition.
我们讨论了定义。
We talked about an example of a method.
我们讨论了一个方法的例子。
Showed you a representation, and perhaps also talked about
给你看了一个表示，也许也谈到
the first idea, too.
了第一个想法。
You've got the representation right, you're
你的表述是正确的，你
often almost done.
通常几乎完成了。
Because with this representation, they can
因为有了这个表示，他们可以
immediately see that there are just two solutions to this
立即看到这个问题只有两种解决方案
problem, something that wouldn't have occurred to us
，这是
when we were little kids, and didn't think to draw the
我们小时候不会想到的，也没有想过要画
[? state ?] diagram.
[? 状态 ?] 图。
There's still one more thing.
还有一件事。
In the past, and in other places, artificial
在过去和其他地方，
intelligence is often taught as purely about reasoning.
人工智能通常被教授为纯粹的推理。
But we solve problems with our eyes, as well as
但是我们用我们的眼睛和
our symbolic apparatus.
我们的象征装置来解决问题。
And you solved that problem with your eyes.
你用眼睛解决了这个问题。
So I like to reinforce that by giving you a little puzzle.
所以我想通过给你一个小谜题来加强这一点。
Let's see, who's here?
让我们看看，谁在这里？
I don't see [? Kambe, ?] but I'll bet he's from Africa.
我没看到 [?  Kambe，？] 但我敢打赌他来自非洲。
Is anyone from Africa?
有人来自非洲吗？
No one's from Africa?
没有人来自非洲？
No?
不？
Well so much the better--
那就更好了——
because they would know the answer to the puzzle.
因为他们会知道谜题的答案。
Here's the puzzle.
这是谜题。 赤道穿过
How many countries in Africa does the Equator cross?
非洲多少个国家？
Would anybody be willing to stake their
有人愿意为
life on their answer?
他们的答案赌上自己的生命吗？
Probably not.
可能不是。
Well, now let me repeat the question.
好吧，现在让我重复这个问题。 赤道穿过
How many countries in Africa does the Equator cross?
非洲多少个国家？
Yeah, six.
是的，六个。
What happened is a miracle.
发生的事情是一个奇迹。
The miracle is that I have communicated with you through
奇迹是我通过语言与你交流，你
language, and your language system commanded your visual
的语言系统命令你的视觉
system to execute a program that involves scanning across
系统执行一个程序，该程序涉及扫描
that line, counting as you go.
那条线，边走边算。
And then your vision system came back to your language
然后你的视觉系统回到你的语言
system and said, six.
系统并说，六。
And that is a miracle.
这是一个奇迹。
And without understanding that miracle, we'll never have a
如果不了解这个奇迹，我们将永远无法
full understanding of the nature of intelligence.
全面了解智能的本质。
But that kind of problem solving is the kind of problem
但是那种解决问题的方法是
solving I wish we could teach you a lot about it.
我希望我们能教给你很多关于它的那种解决方法。
But we can't teach you about stuff we don't understand.
但是我们不能教你我们不理解的东西。
We [INAUDIBLE]
我们 [听不清]
for that.
为此。
That's a little bit about the definition and some examples.
这是关于定义和一些例子的一点点。
What's it for?
这是为了什么？
We can deal with that very quickly.
我们可以很快处理。
If we're engineers, it's for building smarter programs.
如果我们是工程师，那是为了构建更智能的程序。
It's about building a tool kit of representations and methods
它是关于构建一个表示和方法的工具包
that make it possible to build smarter programs.
，使构建更智能的程序成为可能。
And you will find, these days, that you can't build a big
现在你会发现，如果没有将我们在这个主题中讨论的想法嵌入到某个地方，你就无法构建一个大
system without having embedded in it somewhere the ideas that
系统
we talk about in the subject.
。
If you're a scientist, there's a somewhat different
如果您是科学家，则动机有所不同
motivation.
。
But it amounts to studying the same sorts of things.
但这相当于研究同样的事情。
If you're a scientist, you're interested in what it is that
如果你是一名科学家，你会对是什么
enables us to build a computational account of
使我们能够建立智能计算帐户感兴趣
intelligence.
。
That's the part that I do.
这就是我要做的部分。
But most this subject is going to be about the other part,
但是这个主题大部分是关于另一部分的，
the part that makes it possible for you to build
这部分可以让你构建
smarter programs.
更智能的程序。
And some of it will be about what it is that makes us
其中一些将是关于是什么使我们
different from the chimpanzees with whom we share an enormous
与黑猩猩不同，我们与之共享大量
fraction of our DNA.
DNA。
It used to be thought that we share 95% of our DNA with
过去人们认为我们与黑猩猩共享 95% 的 DNA
chimpanzees.
。
Then it went up to 98.
然后它上升到 98。
Thank God it stopped about there.
感谢上帝，它停在那里。
Then it actually went back a little bit.
然后它实际上又回到了一点。
I think we're back down to 94.
我想我们已经回到了 94 年。
How about if we talk a little bit now about the history of
如果我们现在谈谈人工智能的历史
AI, so we can see how we got to where we are today?
怎么样，这样我们就可以看到我们是如何走到今天的？
This will also be a history of AI that tells you a little bit
这也将是一部人工智能的历史，它会告诉你一些
about what you'll learn in this course.
关于你将在本课程中学到的东西。
It all started with Lady Lovelace, the world's first
这一切都始于世界上第一个程序员洛夫莱斯夫人，她在计算机运行
programmer, Who wrote programs about 100 years before there
之前大约 100 年就编写了程序
were computers to run them.
。
But it's interesting that even in 1842, people were hassling
但有趣的是，即使在 1842 年，人们
her about whether computers could get really smart.
还在为计算机是否真的变得聪明而争论不休。
And she said, "The analytical engine has no pretensions to
她说，“分析引擎不会
originate anything.
自命不凡。
It can do whatever we know how to order it to perform."
它可以做我们知道如何命令它执行的任何事情。”
Screwball idea that persists to this day.
一直延续到今天的疯狂想法。
Nevertheless, that was the origin of it all.
然而，这就是这一切的起源。
That was the beginning of the discussions.
那是讨论的开始。
And then nothing much happened until about 1950, when Alan
直到 1950 年左右，艾伦·
Turing wrote his famous paper, which
图灵写下了他著名的论文，
introduced the Turing test.
介绍了图灵测试。
Of course, Alan Turing had previously won the Second
当然，艾伦·图灵此前曾
World War by breaking the German code, the Ultra Code,
通过打破德国密码（Ultra Code）赢得了第二次世界大战
for which the British government rewarded him by
，英国政府为此奖励了他，
driving him to suicide, because he happened to be
迫使他自杀，因为他恰好是
homosexual.
同性恋。
But Turing wrote his paper in 1950, and that was the first
但是图灵在 1950 年写了他的论文，这是
milestone after Lady Lovelace's comment in 1842.
继 1842 年洛夫莱斯夫人发表评论之后的第一个里程碑
And then the modern era really began with a paper written by
。然后，现代时代真正开始
Marvin Minsky in 1960, titled "Steps Toward Artificial
于 1960 年马文·明斯基 (Marvin Minsky) 写的一篇题为“迈向人工智能的步骤”的论文
Intelligence." And it wasn't a long after that Jim
。不久之后，吉姆
[? Slagle, ?]
[?  Slagle，?]
a nearly blind graduate student, wrote a program that
一个几乎失明的研究生，编写了一个
did symbolic integration.
进行符号积分的程序。
Not adding up area under a curve, but doing symbolic
不是把曲线下的面积加起来，
integration just like you learn to do in high school
而是像你在高中一年级时学习做的那样做符号积分
when you're a freshman.
。
Now on Monday, we're going to talk about this program.
现在星期一，我们将讨论这个程序。
And you're going to understand exactly how it works.
你将确切地了解它是如何工作的。
And you can write one yourself.
你可以自己写一个。
And we're going to reach way back in time to look at that
我们将回到过去看看那个
program because, in one day discussing it, talking about
程序，因为有一天讨论它，谈论
it, will be in itself a miniature artificial
它本身就是一门微型
intelligence course.
人工智能课程。
Because it's so rich with important ideas.
因为它有很多重要的想法。
So that's the dawn age, early dawn age.
所以这就是黎明时代，黎明时代。
This was the age of speculation, and this was the
这是投机的时代，也是这里的
dawn age in here.
黎明时代。
So in that early dawn age , the integration program took
因此，在那个黎明时代，整合计划
the world by storm.
席卷了世界。
Because not everybody knows how to do integration.
因为不是每个人都知道如何进行集成。
And someone, everyone, thought that if we can do integration
有人，每个人都认为，如果我们今天可以进行整合
today, the rest of intelligence will be figured
，那么明天剩下的智能就会被计算
out tomorrow.
出来。
Too bad for our side it didn't work out that way.
对我们来说太糟糕了，结果不是这样。
Here's another dawn age program, the Eliza
这是另一个黎明时代的节目，Eliza
[? thing ?].
[? 事物 ？]。
But I imagine you'd prefer a demonstration to
但我想你更喜欢演示而
just reading it, right?
不是阅读它，对吧？
Do you prefer a demonstration?
你喜欢演示吗？
Let's see if we can demonstrate it.
让我们看看我们是否可以证明它。
This is left over from a hamentashen debate of a couple
这是几年前的一场 hamentashen 辩论遗留下来的
of years ago.
。
How do you spell hamentashen, anybody know?
你怎么拼写hametashen，有人知道吗？
I sure hope that's right.
我当然希望这是对的。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。 会有
Something interesting will come.
一些有趣的事情发生。
OK, your choice.
好，你的选择。
Teal?
青色？
Burton House?
伯顿之家？
Teal.
蓝绿色。
So that's dawn age AI.
这就是黎明时代的人工智能。
And no one ever took that stuff seriously, except that
没有人认真对待这些事情，除了制定一些匹配的
it was a fun [INAUDIBLE]
程序是一件有趣的 [听不清]
project level thing to work out some matching
项目级别的事情
programs, and so on.
，等等。
The integration program was serious.
整合计划是严肃的。
This one wasn't.
这个不是。
This was serious, programs that do geometric analogy,
这很严重，做几何类比的程序，
problems of the kind you find on intelligence tests.
你在智力测试中发现的那种问题。
Do you have the answer to this?
你有答案吗？
A is to B as C is to what?
A 之于 B 就像 C 之于什么？
That would be 2, I guess.
那应该是2，我猜。
What's the second best answer?
第二好的答案是什么？
And the theories of the program that solve these
解决这些问题的程序理论
problems are pretty much identical to what you just
与您刚刚发现的几乎相同
figured out.
。
In the first case you deleted the inside figure.
在第一种情况下，您删除了内部图。
And the second case is, the reason you got four is because
第二种情况是，你得到四个的原因是
you deleted the outside part and grew the inside part.
你删除了外部部分并增加了内部部分。
There's another one.
还有一个。
I think this was the hardest one it got, or the easiest one
我认为这是它得到的最难的一个，或者它没有得到的最简单的一个
it didn't get.
I've forgotten.
。 我忘了。
A is to B as C is to 3.
A 之于 B 就像 C 之于 3。
In the late dawn age, we began to turn our attention from
在黎明后期，我们开始将注意力从
purely symbolic reasoning to thinking a little bit about
纯粹的象征性推理转向对感知器的一点思考
perceptual apparatus.
。
And programs were written that could figure out the nature of
并且编写的程序可以弄清楚
shapes and forms, such as that.
形状和形式的本质，例如。
And it's interesting that those programs had the same
有趣的是，这些程序在这
kind of difficulty with this that you do.
方面遇到了和你一样的困难。
Because now, having deleted all the edges, everything
因为现在，删除了所有边缘，一切都
becomes ambiguous.
变得模棱两可。
And it may be a series of platforms, or it may be a
它可能是一系列平台，或者可能是
series of--
一系列——如果你经历反转，
can you see the saw blade sticking up if you go through
你能看到锯片伸出来
the reversal?
吗？
Programs were written that could learn from a small
编写的程序可以从
number of examples.
少量示例中学习。
Many people think of computer learning as involving leading
许多人认为计算机学习涉及引导
some neural net to submission with thousands of trials.
一些神经网络进行数千次试验。
Programs were written in the early dawn age that learned
程序是在黎明时代编写的，
that an arch is something that has to have the flat part on
了解到拱门是顶部必须有平坦部分的东西
top, and the two sides can't touch, and the top may or may
，两侧不能接触，顶部可能是也可能
not be a wedge.
不是楔形。
In the late dawn age, though, the most important thing,
不过，在黎明时分，最重要的事情
perhaps, was what you look at with me on Wednesday next.
也许是你下周三和我一起看的东西。
It's a rule-based expert systems.
这是一个基于规则的专家系统。
And a program was written at Stanford that did diagnosis of
斯坦福大学编写了一个程序来诊断
bacterial infections of the blood.
血液中的细菌感染。
It turned out to do it better than most doctors, most
事实证明，它比大多数医生、大多数
general practitioners.
全科医生做得更好。 奇怪的
It was never used, curiously enough.
是，它从未使用过。
Because nobody cares what your problem actually is.
因为没有人关心你的问题到底是什么。
They just give you a broad spectrum antibiotic that'll
他们只是给你一种广谱抗生素，可以
kill everything.
杀死一切。
But this late dawn age system, the so-called [INAUDIBLE]
但是这个黎明时代的系统，即所谓的 [听不清]
system, was the system that launched a thousand companies,
系统，是启动了一千家公司的系统，
because people started building expert systems built
因为人们开始构建
on that technology.
基于该技术的专家系统。
Here's that you don't know you used, or that was
这是您不知道自己使用过的，或者
used on your behalf.
是代表您使用过的。
If you go through, for example, the Atlanta airport,
例如，如果您经过亚特兰大机场，
your airplane is parked by a rule-based expert system that
您的飞机将由一个基于规则的专家系统停放，该系统
knows how to park aircraft effectively.
知道如何有效地停放飞机。
It saves Delta Airlines about to $0.5 million a day of jet
通过更聪明地停放飞机，达美航空公司每天可以节省大约 50 万美元的喷气
fuel by being all smarter about how to park them.
燃料。
So that's an example of an expert system that does a
这是一个专家系统的例子，
little bit of good for a lot of people.
它对很多人都有点好处。
There's Deep Blue.
有深蓝。
That takes us to the next stage beyond the age of expert
这将我们带到了超越专家
systems, and the business age.
系统时代和商业时代的下一个阶段。
It takes us into this age here, which I call the
它把我们带到了这个时代，我称之为
bulldozer age, because this is the time when people began to
推土机时代，因为这是人们开始
see that we had at our disposal
看到我们拥有
unlimited amounts of computing.
无限量计算的时代。
And frequently you can substitute computing for
通常，您可以用计算代替
intelligence.
智能。
So no one would say that Deep Blue does anything like what a
所以没有人会说深蓝做的事情就像
human chess master does.
人类国际象棋大师所做的那样。
But nevertheless, Deep Blue, by processing data like a
但尽管如此，深蓝通过像
bulldozer processes gravel, was able to
推土机处理砾石一样处理数据，还是能够
beat the world champion.
击败世界冠军。
So what's the right way?
那么正确的方法是什么？
That's the age we're in right now.
这就是我们现在所处的时代。
I will of course be inducing programs for those ages as we
当我们讨论这个主题时，我当然会为那些年龄段的人制定计划
go through the subject.
。
There is a question of what age we're in right now.
有一个问题是我们现在处于什么时代。
And it's always dangerous to name an age when
you're in it, I guess.
我猜，当你身处其中时，说出一个时代总是很危险的。
I like to call at the age of the right way.
我喜欢在正确的年龄打电话。
And this is an age when we begin to realize that that
这是一个我们开始意识到上面的
definition up there is actually a little incomplete,
定义实际上有点不完整的时代，
because much of our intelligence has to do not
因为我们的大部分智力
with thinking, perception, and action acting separately, but
与思考、感知和行动无关，而是
with loops that tie all those together.
与将所有这些联系在一起的循环有关。
We had one example with Africa.
我们有一个非洲的例子。
Here's another example drawn from a program that has been
这是另一个示例，该示例取自我的实验室中一直
under development, and continues to be, in my
在开发并继续开发的程序
laboratory.
。
We're going to ask the system to imagine something.
我们将要求系统想象一些东西。
SYSTEM: OK.
系统：好的。
I will imagine that a ball falls into a bowl.
我会想象一个球掉进碗里。
OK.
好的。
I will imagine that a man runs into a woman.
我会想象一个男人遇到一个女人。
PATRICK WINSTON: You see, it does the best that it can if
PATRICK WINSTON：你看，如果
it doesn't have a good memory of what these situations
它对这些情况
actually involve.
实际涉及的内容没有很好的记忆，它会尽力而为。
But having imagined the scene it can then--
但是想象一下场景之后它可以——
SYSTEM: Yes.
系统：是的。
I have learned from experience that contact between a man and
我从经验中了解到，男人和女人之间的接触是
a woman appeared because a man runs into a woman.
因为男人遇到女人而出现的。
PATRICK WINSTON: Having imagined the scene, it can
PATRICK WINSTON：在想象了场景之后，它可以
then read the answers using its visual apparatus on the
使用
scene that it imagined.
它想象的场景中的视觉设备来阅读答案。
So just like what you did with Africa, only now it's working
所以就像你对非洲所做的那样，只是现在它正在
with its own visual memory, using visual programs.
使用自己的视觉记忆，使用视觉程序。
SYSTEM: OK.
系统：好的。
I will imagine that a man gives a ball to a man.
我会想象一个男人给一个男人一个球。
PATRICK WINSTON: I know this looks like slugs, but they're
PATRICK WINSTON：我知道这看起来像蛞蝓，但他们
actually distinguished professors.
实际上是杰出的教授。
It always does the best it can.
它总是尽力而为。
SYSTEM: OK.
系统：好的。
I will imagine that a man flies.
我会想象一个人会飞。
PATRICK WINSTON: It's the best that it can do.
PATRICK WINSTON：这是它所能做的最好的。
So that concludes our discussion of the history.
我们对历史的讨论到此结束。 随着学期的展开
And I've provided you with a little bit of a glimpse of
，我已经为您提供了一些
what we're going to look at as the semester unfolds.
我们将要研究的内容的一瞥。
Yes, Chris?
是的，克里斯？
CHRIS: Is it actually a demonstration of something?
克里斯：它实际上是在展示什么吗？
Does it have a large database of videos?
它有一个庞大的视频数据库吗？
PATRICK WINSTON: No, it has a small database videos.
PATRICK WINSTON：不，它有一个小型数据库视频。
CHRIS: But it's intelligently picking among them based on--
CHRIS：但它是根据--
PATRICK WINSTON: Based on their content.
PATRICK WINSTON：根据他们的内容明智地在其中挑选的。
So if you say imagine that a student gave a ball to another
所以如果你说想象一个学生给了另一个学生一个球
student, it imagines that.
，它就是想象出来的。
You say, now does the other student have the ball?
你说，现在其他学生有球吗？
Does the other student take the ball?
其他学生接球了吗？
It can answer those questions because it can review the same
它可以回答这些问题，因为它可以查看同一
video and see the take as well as the give in the same video.
视频并查看同一视频中的取舍。
So now we have to think about why we ought to be optimistic
所以现在我们必须思考为什么我们应该对未来保持
about the future.
乐观。
Because we've had a long history here, and we haven't
因为我们这里历史悠久，我们还没有
solved the problem.
解决问题。
But one reason why we can feel optimistic about future is
但我们对未来感到乐观的一个原因是
because all of our friends have been on the march.
因为我们所有的朋友都在前进。
And our friends include the cognitive psychologists, the
我们的朋友包括认知心理学家、
[? developmental ?]
[? 发展？]
psychologists, the linguists, sometimes the philosophers,
心理学家，语言学家，有时是哲学家
and especially the paleoanthropologists.
，尤其是古人类学家。
Because it is becoming increasingly clear why we're
因为越来越清楚为什么我们
actually different from the chimpanzees, and how we got to
实际上与黑猩猩不同，以及我们如何
be that way.
成为那样。
The high school idea is that we evolved through slow,
高中的理念是我们通过缓慢、
gradual, and continuous improvement.
渐进和持续的改进而进化。
But that doesn't seem to be the way it happened.
但事情似乎并非如此。
There are some characteristics of our species that are
在指导像我这样的人的活动时，我们物种的一些特征可以提供
informative when it comes to guiding the activities of
丰富的信息
people like me.
。
And here's what the story seems to be
这就是
from the fossil record.
化石记录中的故事。
First of all, we humans have been around for maybe 200,000
首先，以我们目前的解剖形式，我们人类已经存在了大约 20
years in our present anatomical form.
万年。
If someone walked through the door right now from 200,000
如果有人现在从 20 万
years ago, I imagine they would be dirty,
年前走进这扇门，我想他们会很脏，
but other than that--
但除此之外——
probably naked, too--
可能也赤身裸体——
other than that, you wouldn't be able to tell the
除此之外，你将无法
difference, especially at MIT.
区分，尤其是在麻省理工学院 .
And so the ensuing 150,000 years was a period in which we
所以接下来的 150,000 年是一个我们
humans didn't actually amount to much.
人类实际上并不多的时期。
But somehow, shortly before 50,000 years ago, some small
但不知何故，在50,000 年前不久，
group of us developed a capability that separated us
我们中的一小部分人发展了一种能力，将我们
from all other species.
与所有其他物种区分开来。
It was an accident of evolution.
这是进化的意外。
And these accidents may or may not happen, but it happened to
这些事故可能会发生也可能不会发生，但它恰好
produce us.
产生了我们。
It's also the case that we probably necked down as a
情况也是如此，我们作为一个物种可能缩小
species to a few thousand, or maybe even a few hundred
到几千，甚至几百个
individuals, something which made these accidental changes,
个体，这使得这些偶然的变化，
accidental evolutionary products,
偶然的进化产物，
more capable of sticking.
更有能力坚持下去。
This leads us to speculate on what it was that happened
这使我们推测
50,000 years ago.
50,000 年前发生了什么。
And paleoanthropologists, Noam Chomsky, a lot of people
和古人类学家诺姆·乔姆斯基（NoamChomsky）一样，很多人
reached similar conclusions.
也得出了类似的结论。
And that conclusion is--
这个结论是——
I'll quote Chomsky.
我会引用乔姆斯基的话。
He's the voice of authority.
他是权威的声音。
"It seems that shortly before 50,000 years ago, some small
“似乎在五万年前不久，
group of us acquired the ability to take two concepts,
我们中的一小部分人获得了将两个
and combine them to make a third concept, without
概念结合起来形成第三个概念的能力，而不会
disturbing the original two concepts, without limit." And
干扰原来的两个概念，没有限制。”
from a perspective of an AI person like me, what Chomsky
从像我这样的人工智能人的角度来看，乔姆斯基
seems to be saying is, we learned how to begin to
似乎在说，我们学会了如何开始
describe things, in a way that was intimately
描述事物，以一种
connected with language.
与语言密切相关的方式。
And that, in the end, is what separates us from the
最后，这就是我们与
chimpanzees.
黑猩猩的区别。
So you might say, well let's just study language.
所以你可能会说，好吧，让我们学习语言吧。
No, you can't do that, because we think with our eyes.
不，你不能那样做，因为我们用眼睛思考。
So language does two things.
所以语言做了两件事。
Number one, it enables us to make descriptions.
第一，它使我们能够进行描述。
Descriptions enable us to tell stories.
描述使我们能够讲述故事。
And storytelling and story understanding is what all of
讲故事和理解故事是所有
education is about.
教育的目的。
That's going up.
那正在上升。
And going down enables us to marshal the resources of our
下降使我们能够整合我们感知系统的资源
perceptual systems, and even command our perceptual systems
，甚至命令我们的感知
to imagine things we've never seen.
系统想象我们从未见过的事物。
So here's an example.
所以这里有一个例子。
Imagine running down the street with a
想象一下提着
full bucket of water.
满满一桶水在街上奔跑。
What happens?
怎么了？
Your leg gets wet.
你的腿湿了。
The water sloshes out.
水溅出来了。
You'll never find that fact anywhere on the web.
你永远不会在网络上的任何地方找到这个事实。
You've probably never been told that that's what happens
你可能从来没有被告知，
when you run down the street with a full bucket of water.
当你带着满满一桶水跑到街上时会发生这种情况。
But you easily imagine this scenario, and you know what's
但是您很容易想象这种情况，并且您知道
going to happen.
会发生什么。
There was internal imagination simulation.
有内部想象模拟。
We're never going to understand human intelligence
在我们能够理解之前，我们永远不会理解人类的智能
until we can understand that.
。
Here's another example.
这是另一个例子。
Imagine running down the street with a
想象一下带着
full bucket of nickels?
满满一桶镍币在街上奔跑？
What happens?
怎么了？
Nickels weigh a lot.
镍很重。
You're going to be bent over.
你会弯腰的。
You're going to stagger.
你会摇摇晃晃的。
But nobody ever told you that.
但从来没有人告诉过你。
You won't find it anywhere on the web.
你不会在网络上的任何地方找到它。
So language is at the center of things because it enables
所以语言是事物的中心，因为它使
storytelling going up, and marshalling the resources of
讲故事上升，并整合感知装置的资源
the perceptual apparatus, going down.
，下降。
And that's where we're going to finish the subject the
这就是我们要
semester, by trying to understand more about that
通过尝试更多地了解这种
phenomenon.
现象来完成这个学期的主题。
So that concludes everything I wanted to say about the
至此，我想说的关于
material and the subject.
材料和主题的一切都结束了。
Now I want to turn my attention a little bit to how
现在我想把注意力转移到
we are going to operate the subject.
我们将如何操作这个主题上。
Because there are many characteristics of the subject
因为该主题
that are confusing.
有许多令人困惑的特征。
First of all, we have four kinds of
首先，我们
activities in the course.
在课程中有四种活动。
And each of these has a different purpose.
而且每一个都有不同的目的。
So I did the lectures.
所以我做了讲座。
And the lectures are supposed to be an hour about
讲座应该是一个小时，
introducing the material and the big picture.
介绍材料和大局。
They're about powerful ideas.
它们是关于强大的想法。
They're about the experience side of the course.
它们是关于课程的体验方面的。
Let me step aside and make a remark.
让我靠边说一下。
MIT is about two things.
麻省理工学院有两件事。
It's about skill building, and it's about big ideas.
这是关于技能的培养，是关于伟大的想法。
So you can build a skill at home, or at Dartmouth, or at
所以你可以在家里、达特茅斯、
Harvard, or Princeton, or all those kinds of places.
哈佛、普林斯顿或所有这些地方培养技能。
But the experience you can only get at MIT.
但是你只能在麻省理工学院获得经验。
I know everybody there is to know in artificial
我知道每个人都知道
intelligence.
人工智能。
I can tell you about how they think.
我可以告诉你他们的想法。
I can tell you about how I think.
我可以告诉你我的想法。
And that's something you're not going to
这是您在
get any other place.
其他任何地方都无法获得的东西。
So that's my role, as I see it, in giving these lectures.
在我看来，这就是我在进行这些讲座时的角色。
Recitations are four buttressing and expanding on
背诵是对材料的四个支撑和扩展
the material, and providing a venue that's small enough for
，并提供一个足够小的
discussion.
讨论场所。
Mega recitations are [? a usual ?]
超级朗诵是[？ 一个通常的？]
components of the course.
课程的组成部分。
They're taught at the same hour on Fridays.
他们在周五的同一时间上课。
Mark Seifter, my graduate student,
我的研究生 Mark Seifter
will be teaching those.
将教授这些。
And those are wrapped around past quiz problems.
这些都围绕着过去的测验问题。
And Mark will show you how to work them.
马克会告诉你如何使用它们。
It's very important component to the subject.
这是该主题非常重要的组成部分。
And finally the tutorials are about helping
最后，教程是关于帮助
you with the homework.
您完成作业的。
So you might say to me, well, do I really
所以你可能会对我说，好吧，我真的
need to go to class?
需要去上课吗？
I like to say that the answer is, only if you like to pass
我想说答案是，只有当你喜欢
the subject.
通过主题时。
But you are MIT students.
但你们是麻省理工学院的学生。
And MIT people always like to look at the data.
麻省理工学院的人总是喜欢看数据。
So this is a scattergram we made after the subject was
所以这是我们去年秋天讲完这门课后做的散点图
taught last fall, which shows the relationship between
，它显示
attendance at lectures and the grades awarded in the course.
了听课和课程成绩之间的关系。
And if you're not sure what that all means, here's the
如果你不确定这一切意味着什么，这里是
regression line.
回归线。
So that information is a little suspect for two
所以这个信息有点可疑，有两个
reasons, one of which is we asked people to self report on
原因，其中一个是我们要求人们自我报告
how many lectures they thought they attended.
他们认为他们参加了多少讲座。
And our mechanism for assigning these numerical
我们分配这些数字
grades is a little weird.
等级的机制有点奇怪。
And there's a third thing, too, and that is, one must
还有第三件事，那就是
never confuse correlation with cause.
永远不要将相关性与原因混为一谈。
You can think of other explanations for why that
对于该
trend line goes up, different from whether it has something
趋势线为何上升，您可以考虑其他解释，与它
to do with lectures producing good grades.
是否与产生好成绩的讲座有关。
You might ask how I feel about the people up there on the
你可能会问我对
other upper left hand corner.
另一个左上角的人感觉如何。
There are one or two people who were near the top of the
有一两个人接近主题的顶部
subject who didn't go to class at all.
，根本没有去上课。
And I have mixed feelings about that.
我对此有复杂的感觉。
You're adults.
你们是成年人。
It's your call.
这是你的电话。
On the other hand, I wish that if that's what you do
另一方面，我希望如果这是你在麻省理工学院
habitually in all the subjects you take at MIT, that you
学习的所有科目的习惯做法，你
would resign and go somewhere else, and let somebody else
会辞职并去其他地方，让其他人
take their slot.
占据他们的位置。
Because you're not benefiting from the powerful ideas, and
因为你没有从强大的想法
the other kinds of things that involve
以及其他涉及
interaction with faculty.
与教师互动的事情中受益。
So it can be done.
所以可以做到。
But I don't recommend it.
但我不推荐它。
By the way, all of the four activities that we have here
顺便说一句，我们在这里的所有四项活动都
show similar regression lines.
显示出相似的回归线。
But what about that five point scale?
但是那个五点量表呢？
Let me explain how that works to you.
让我解释一下它是如何对你起作用的。
We love to have people ask us what the class
我们喜欢让人们
average is on a quiz.
在测验中问我们班级平均水平是多少。
Because that's when we get to use our blank stare.
因为那是我们开始使用空白凝视的时候。
Because we have no idea what the class average
因为我们不知道任何测验的班级平均
ever is on any quiz.
水平。
Here's what we do.
这就是我们所做的。
Like everybody else, we start off with a score
和其他人一样，我们一开始的分数是
from zero to 100.
从 0 到 100。
But then we say to ourselves, what score would you get if
但后来我们对自己说，如果
you had a thorough understanding of the material?
你对材料有透彻的理解，你会得到多少分？
And we say, well, for this particular exam, it's this
我们说，好吧，对于这个特殊的考试，这个
number right here.
数字就在这里。
And what score would you get if you had a good
如果你对材料有很好的
understanding of the material?
理解，你会得到什么分数？
That's that score.
就是这个分数。
And what happens if you're down here is that you're
如果你在这里会发生什么是你正在
following off the edge of the range in which we think you
跟随我们认为你
need to do more work.
需要做更多工作的范围的边缘。
So what we do is, we say that if you're in this range here--
所以我们所做的是，我们说，如果你在这个范围内——
following MIT convention with GPAs and stuff,
遵循 MIT 约定的 GPA 和其他东西，
that gets you a five.
那你就得了 5 分。
If you're in this range down here, there's a
如果你在这个范围内，就会
sharp drop off to four.
急剧下降到四。
If you're in this range down here, there's a
如果你在这个范围内，就会
sharp fall off to three.
急剧下降到三个。
So that means if you're in the middle of one of those
因此，这意味着如果您处于其中一个高原的中间，那么
plateaus there's no point in arguing with this.
与此争论是没有意义的。
Because it's not going to do you any good.
因为这对你没有任何好处。
We have these boundaries where we think performance break
我们有这些边界，我们认为是性能
points are.
断点所在。
So you say, well that seems a little harsh.
所以你说，嗯，这似乎有点苛刻。
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, and start arguing.
废话，废话，废话，废话，废话，然后开始争论。
But then we will come back with a second major innovation
但随后我们将带着课程中的第二个重大创新回来
we have in the course.
。
That is that your grade is calculated in several parts.
那就是你的成绩是分几个部分计算的。
Part one is the max of your grade on Q1, and
第一部分是Q1 的最高分，也是期末考试的第一
part one of the final.
部分。
So in other words, you get two shots at everything.
所以换句话说，你在任何事情上都有两枪。
So if you have complete glorious undeniable horrible F
因此，如果您在第一次测验中获得了完全光荣的不可否认的可怕 F
on the first quiz, it gets erased on the final if you do
，那么如果您在决赛的
well on that part of the final.
那部分表现出色，它就会在决赛中被抹去。
So each quiz has a corresponding
所以每个测验
mirror on the final.
在决赛上都有对应的镜子。
You get the max of the score you got on those two pieces.
你得到你在这两件上得到的最高分。
And now you say to me, I'm an MIT student.
现在你对我说，我是麻省理工学院的学生。
I have a lot of guts.
我有很大的胆量。
I'm only going to take the final.
我只会参加决赛。
It has been done.
它已经完成。
We don't recommend it.
我们不推荐它。
And the reason we don't recommend it is that we don't
我们不推荐它的原因是我们不
expect everybody to do all of the final.
希望每个人都完成所有决赛。
So there would be a lot of time pressure if you had to do
因此，如果您必须完成
all of the final, all five parts of the final.
所有决赛，决赛的所有五个部分，将会有很大的时间压力。
So we have four quizzes.
所以我们有四个测验。
And the final has a fifth part because there's some material
期末考试有第五部分，因为
that we teach you after the last date on which we can give
在最后日期之后我们会教给你一些材料，我们可以
you a final by institute rules.
根据学院规则为你提供期末考试。
But that's roughly how it works.
但这大致就是它的工作原理。
And you can read about more of the details in the FAQ on the
您可以在主题主页上的常见问题解答中阅读更多详细信息
subject homepage.
。
So now we're almost done.
所以现在我们差不多完成了。
I just want to talk a little bit about how we're going to
我只是想谈谈接下来几天我们将如何
communicate with you in the next few days, while we're
与您沟通，同时我们
getting ourselves organized.
正在整理自己。
So, number one-- if I could ask the TAs to help me pass
所以，第一——如果我可以请助教帮我把
these out--
这些传出去——
we need to schedule you into tutorials.
我们需要安排你参加教程。
So we're going to ask you to fill out this form, and give
因此，我们将要求您填写此表格，并
it to us before you leave.
在您离开之前将其交给我们。
So you'll be hearing from us once we do the sort.
因此，一旦我们进行排序，您就会收到我们的来信。
There's the issue of whether we're going to have ordinary
问题是我们这周是要进行普通的
recitation and a mega recitation this week.
朗诵和大型的朗诵。
So pay attention.
所以要注意。
Otherwise, you're going to be stranded in a classroom with
否则，你将被困在教室里
nothing to do.
无所事事。 这周
We're not going to have any regular recitations this week.
我们不会有任何定期的朗诵。
Are we having regular recitation this week,
我们这周有定期朗诵
[INAUDIBLE]?
吗，[听不清]？
No.
不。
We may, and probably will, have a mega recitation this
我们可能而且可能会在
week that's devoted to a Python review.
本周举行一场专门针对 Python 评论的大型朗诵会。
Now we know that there are many of you who are
现在我们知道有很多人在周五
celebrating a religious holiday on Friday, and so we
庆祝宗教节日，因此我们
will be putting a lot of resources online so you can
将在网上放置大量资源，以便您可以
get that review in another way.
通过另一种方式获得该评论。
We probably will have a Python review on Friday.
我们可能会在周五进行 Python评测。
And we ask that you look at our home page for further
随着一周的进行，我们要求您查看我们的主页以获取更多
information about that as the week progresses.
信息。
So that's all folks.
所以这就是所有的人。
That concludes what we're going to do today.
我们今天要做的事情到此结束。
And as soon as you give us your form, we're through.
只要你给我们你的表格，我们就完成了。